const generateCommonTags = () => [
	'custom',
	'online',
	'tool',
	'free',
	'website'
];

export const convertFromMarkdownToHTMLTool = {
	relativePath: 'convert-from-markdown-to-html',
	title:
		'Markdown to HTML Converter - Quickly and Easily Convert Your Markdown Text to HTML',
	shortTitle: 'Markdown to HTML Converter',
	description:
		'Use our simple and user-friendly Markdown to HTML converter to quickly and easily convert your markdown text to HTML. Simply type your markdown text in the textarea and see the output in real-time, and easily copy the HTML output to your clipboard.',
	shortDescription:
		'Convert markdown text to HTML with our user-friendly tool.',
	tags: ['markdown', 'html', 'converter', 'convert', ...generateCommonTags()],
	questionsAndAnswers: [
		{
			question: 'How do I use your Markdown to HTML converter?',
			answer:
				'To use our Markdown to HTML converter, simply type your markdown text in the textarea provided on the page, and the output HTML will be displayed in real-time. You can then easily copy the HTML output to your clipboard by clicking the "Copy HTML" button.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I customize the HTML output from the converter?',
			answer:
				'Our Markdown to HTML converter does not currently offer any customization options for the HTML output. However, you can easily edit the HTML after it has been converted to make any desired changes.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the Markdown to HTML converter free to use?',
			answer:
				'Yes, our Markdown to HTML converter is completely free to use. You do not need to create an account or provide any personal information to use the converter.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the Markdown to HTML converter accurate?',
			answer:
				'We have tested our Markdown to HTML converter extensively and it should produce accurate results. If you encounter any issues or errors, please contact us and we will do our best to resolve them.'
		},
		{
			question:
				'Can I use the Markdown to HTML converter for commercial purposes?',
			answer:
				'Yes, you are welcome to use our Markdown to HTML converter for commercial purposes. There are no usage restrictions or limitations.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the converter free to use?',
			answer: 'Yes, the converter is completely free to use.'
		},
		{
			question: 'How do I copy the HTML output to my clipboard?',
			answer:
				'To copy the HTML output to your clipboard, you can use the "Copy" button provided on the page. Alternatively, you can use your browser\'s native copy functionality, such as right-clicking on the output and selecting "Copy" or using the keyboard shortcut Ctrl+C (on Windows) or Command+C (on Mac).'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I save the HTML output to a file?',
			answer:
				'Yes, you can save the HTML output to a file by using your browser\'s "Save As" functionality, such as right-clicking on the page and selecting "Save As" or using the keyboard shortcut Ctrl+S (on Windows) or Command+S (on Mac).'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the converter mobile-friendly?',
			answer:
				'Yes, the converter is designed to be mobile-friendly and should work on most devices and screen sizes.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Are there any limitations to the converter?',
			answer:
				'There are no limitations to the converter. You can use it to convert as much markdown text to HTML as you like.'
		}
	],
	mainTag: 'converter'
};

export const textToURLSlugConverterTool = {
	relativePath: 'text-to-url-slug-converter',
	title:
		'Text to URL Slug Converter - Convert your text to a unique and SEO-friendly URL slug',
	shortTitle: 'Text to URL Slug Converter',
	description:
		'Easily convert your text to a unique and SEO-friendly URL slug with our online converter tool. Simply type your text into the input field and copy the generated slug to use on your website or blog.',
	shortDescription:
		'Convert your text to a unique and SEO-friendly URL slug with our online converter tool.',
	tags: [
		'slug',
		'url',
		'text',
		'converter',
		'convert',
		...generateCommonTags()
	],
	questionsAndAnswers: [
		{
			question: 'How do I use the text to URL slug converter?',
			answer:
				'To use the text to URL slug converter, simply type your text into the input field and click the "Convert" button. The generated URL slug will appear below the input field.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the converter free to use?',
			answer: 'Yes, the converter is free to use.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I convert multiple pieces of text at once?',
			answer:
				'No, the converter only allows you to convert one piece of text at a time.'
		},
		{
			question: 'How do I copy the generated URL slug to my clipboard?',
			answer:
				'To copy the generated URL slug to your clipboard, click the "Copy" button next to the URL slug.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I customize the generated URL slug?',
			answer:
				'No, the generated URL slug is automatically created based on the input text and cannot be customized. However, you can customize the input text to create a desired URL slug.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the converter mobile-friendly?',
			answer:
				'Yes, the converter is mobile-friendly and can be used on any device with a web browser.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Are there any limitations to the converter?',
			answer:
				"There are no limitations to the converter, you can convert as much text as you want. However, it's recommended to keep the length of the generated URL slug within a reasonable range for optimal SEO and readability."
		},
		{
			question:
				'How does the converter ensure the generated URL slug is unique and SEO-friendly?',
			answer:
				'The converter uses a combination of algorithms and heuristics to generate unique and SEO-friendly URL slugs. This includes removing special characters, converting spaces to hyphens, and lowercasing the text.'
		},
		{
			question:
				'Can I use the generated URL slug on any platform or only on certain websites?',
			answer:
				'You can use the generated URL slug on any platform that supports custom URL slugs. This includes websites, blogs, and even social media platforms.'
		},
		{
			question: 'How do I know if my generated URL slug is SEO-friendly?',
			answer:
				'There are several factors that contribute to a URL slug being SEO-friendly, such as length, readability, and keyword relevance. You can use an SEO tool or consult with an SEO specialist to determine the SEO-friendliness of your generated URL slug.'
		}
	],
	mainTag: 'converter'
};

export const textToQRCodeConverterTool = {
	relativePath: 'text-to-qr-code-converter',
	title:
		'Text to QR Code Converter - Quickly and Easily Convert Your Text to a QR Code',
	shortTitle: 'Text to QR Code Converter',
	description:
		'Use our simple and user-friendly Text to QR Code converter to quickly and easily convert your text to a QR code. Simply type your text in the textarea, click the generate button, and scan the generated QR code with your smartphone or QR code reader.',
	shortDescription:
		'Quickly and easily convert your text to a QR code with our online converter tool.',
	tags: [
		'text',
		'qr-code',
		'converter',
		'convert',
		'generate',
		...generateCommonTags()
	],
	questionsAndAnswers: [
		{
			question: 'How do I use the Text to QR Code converter?',
			answer:
				'To use the Text to QR Code converter, simply type your text in the textarea provided and click the generate button. The QR code will be displayed on the page, and you can scan it with a smartphone or QR code reader.'
		},

		{
			question: 'Is the converter free to use?',
			answer: 'Yes, the Text to QR Code converter is completely free to use.'
		},

		{
			question: 'Can I convert multiple pieces of text at once?',
			answer:
				'Unfortunately, the Text to QR Code converter currently only allows you to convert one piece of text at a time. However, you can easily convert multiple pieces of text by simply repeating the process for each piece of text you want to convert.'
		},

		{
			question: 'How do I scan the generated QR code?',
			answer:
				'To scan the generated QR code, simply use the camera on your smartphone or a QR code reader device to scan the code. The text that was encoded in the QR code will be displayed on your device.'
		},

		{
			question: 'Can I customize the appearance of the generated QR code?',
			answer:
				'The Text to QR Code converter currently does not offer customization options for the appearance of the generated QR code. However, you can use a different QR code generator tool that offers customization options if you need to customize the appearance of your QR code.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the converter mobile-friendly?',
			answer:
				'Yes, the converter is mobile-friendly and can be used on any device with a web browser.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Are there any limitations to the converter?',
			answer:
				"There may be limitations to the amount of text that can be converted to a QR code, depending on the size and complexity of the text. It's also important to note that QR codes have a maximum capacity and may not be able to hold very large amounts of data."
		},
		{
			question:
				'How does the converter ensure the generated QR code is readable by QR code scanners?',
			answer:
				'The converter uses a reliable QR code generator library to generate the QR code, ensuring that it is properly formatted and optimized for readability by QR code scanners.'
		},
		{
			question:
				'Can I use the generated QR code on any platform or only on certain websites?',
			answer:
				'You can use the generated QR code on any platform or website that supports QR code scanning.'
		},
		{
			question:
				'How do I know if my generated QR code is readable by QR code scanners?',
			answer:
				'You can test the readability of your generated QR code by scanning it with a QR code scanner app on your smartphone or other device. If the QR code is readable, the scanner should be able to successfully interpret and display the encoded data.'
		}
	],
	mainTag: ''
};

export const generateFractalTreeTool = {
	relativePath: 'generate-fractal-tree',
	title: 'Generate Beautiful Fractal Trees with Our Online Tool',
	shortTitle: 'Fractal Tree Generator',
	description:
		'Our online tool allows you to generate stunning fractal trees with custom parameters or randomly generated values. Explore the infinite possibilities of fractal tree design and create your own unique creations!',
	shortDescription:
		'Generate beautiful fractal trees with custom or random parameters with our online tool.',
	tags: [
		'fractal-tree',
		'generator',
		'computer-generated-arts',
		'generate',
		'random',
		'design',
		'unique',
		...generateCommonTags()
	],
	questionsAndAnswers: [
		{
			question: 'How do I use the fractal tree generator?',
			answer:
				'Simply enter your desired parameters or choose to generate a random tree, and hit the "Generate" button to see your fractal tree design.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I customize the parameters of my fractal tree?',
			answer:
				'Yes, you can adjust the branch length, branch angle, and recursion depth to create the exact fractal tree you want.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I save my fractal tree designs?',
			answer:
				'Yes, you can download your fractal tree as an image file or save it to your account for later use.'
		},
		{
			question: 'How many different fractal tree designs can I create?',
			answer:
				'With the customizable parameters and the ability to generate random trees, the possibilities are virtually infinite. Explore and create your own unique fractal tree designs.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the fractal tree generator free to use?',
			answer: 'Yes, our fractal tree generator is completely free to use.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Is the fractal tree generator mobile-friendly?',
			answer:
				'Yes, our fractal tree generator is fully optimized for use on mobile devices.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Are there any limitations to the fractal tree generator?',
			answer:
				'There are no limitations to the number of fractal trees you can generate or the parameters you can use. Explore and create as many designs as you like.'
		},
		{
			question:
				'Can I share my fractal tree designs on social media or other platforms?',
			answer:
				"Yes, you can share your fractal tree designs on social media or other platforms by saving the design and uploading it to the platform of your choice, just don't forget to give us the credit"
		},
		{
			question:
				'How do I know which parameters will create the best fractal tree design?',
			answer:
				'Experimenting with different parameter values and previewing the generated fractal tree can help you determine which parameters will create the best design for your needs.'
		},
		{
			question: 'Can I use the fractal tree generator for commercial purposes?',
			answer:
				"Yes, you can use the fractal tree generator for commercial purposes, just don't forget to give us the credit."
		},
		{
			question:
				'How is the random fractal tree generator different from using custom parameters?',
			answer:
				'The random fractal tree generator creates a unique fractal tree design using randomly generated values for the parameters, while using custom parameters allows you to specify specific values for the parameters to generate a fractal tree.'
		},
		{
			question: 'How do I know if my fractal tree design is unique?',
			answer:
				'You can compare your fractal tree design to other designs generated by the tool to determine if it is unique, or you can use a search engine to check if the design has been used elsewhere online.'
		},
		{
			questions: 'How does the fractal tree generator ensure unique designs?',
			answers:
				'The fractal tree generator uses advanced algorithms to generate unique designs based on the parameters or random values inputted.'
		},
		{
			questions:
				'How does the depth of the fractal tree affect its appearance?',
			answers:
				'The depth of the fractal tree affects its appearance by determining how many iterations of the branching pattern are drawn. A deeper fractal tree will have more branches and a more complex appearance, while a shallower tree will have fewer branches and a simpler appearance.'
		},
		{
			questions:
				'What are some creative ways to use fractal trees in design projects?',
			answers:
				'Some creative ways to use fractal trees in design projects include using them as backgrounds, incorporating them into logos or graphics, and using them as inspiration for hand-drawn art.'
		}
	],
	mainTag: 'computer-generated-arts'
};

const toolsData = {
	basePath: '/tools',
	pages: [
		textToURLSlugConverterTool,
		textToQRCodeConverterTool,
		convertFromMarkdownToHTMLTool,
		generateFractalTreeTool
	]
};

export default toolsData;

// <meta name="revisit-after" content="7 days">: This tag tells search engines how often to revisit the page for updates.
/*
export const tempTool = {
	relativePath: '',
	title: '',
	shortTitle: '',
	description: '',
	shortDescription: '',
	tags: ['markdown', 'html', 'converter', 'convert', ...generateCommonTags()],
	mainTag: ''
};
*/
